Guide to the Archives Union File Part 2, Section 3: Boxes 130-143 1872-1976
Archives Union File Part 2, Section 3: Boxes 130-143
- Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1906-1907 (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Item 37: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.38 (1907: July 19)
  - Item 38: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.39 (1907: July 26)
  - Item 39: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.40 (1907: Aug. 2)
  - Item 40: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.41 (1907: Aug. 9)
    Language: English; Yiddish.
  - Item 41: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.42 (1907: Aug. 16)
  - Item 42: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.43 (1907: Aug. 23)
  - Item 43: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.45 (1907: Sept. 6)
  - Item 44: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.46 (1907: Sept. 13)
  - Item 45: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.47 (1907: Sept. 20)
  - Item 46: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.48 (1907: Sept. 27)
  - Item 47: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.49 (1907: Oct. 4)
  - Item 48: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.50 (1907: Oct. 11)
  - Item 49: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.51 (1907: Oct. 18)
  - Item 50: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.52 (1907: Oct. 25)
- Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907-1908 (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.1 (1907: Nov. 1)
  - Item 2: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.2 (1907: Nov. 8)
  - Item 3: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.3 (1907: Nov. 15)
  - Item 4: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.4 (1907: Nov. 22)
  - Item 5: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.5 (1907: Nov. 29)
  - Item 6: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.6 (1907: Dec. 6)
  - Item 7: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.7 (1907: Dec. 13)
  - Item 8: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.8 (1907: Dec. 20)
  - Item 9: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.9 (1907: Dec. 27)
  - Item 10: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.10 (1908: Jan. 3)
  - Item 11: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.11 (1908: Jan. 10)
  - Item 12: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.12 (1908: Jan. 17)
  - Item 13: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.13 (1908: Jan. 24)
  - Item 14: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.14 (1908: Jan. 31)
  - Item 15: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.15 (1908: Feb. 7)
  - Item 16: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.16 (1908: Feb. 14)
  - Item 17: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.17 (1908: Feb. 21)
  - Item 18: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.18 (1908: Feb. 28)
  - Item 19: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.19 (1908: Mar. 6)
  - Item 20: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.20 (1908: Mar. 13)
  - Item 21: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.21 (1908: Mar. 20)
  - Item 22: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.22 (1908: Mar. 27)
  - Item 23: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.23 (1908: Apr. 3)
  - Item 24: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.24 (1908: Apr. 10)
  - Item 25: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.25 (1908: Apr. 17)
  - Item 26: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.26 (1908: Apr. 24)
  - Item 27: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.27 (1908: May 1)
  - Item 28: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.28 (1908: May 8)
  - Item 29: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.29 (1908: May 15)
  - Item 30: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.30 (1908: May 22)
  - Item 31: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.31 (1908: May 29)
  - Item 32: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.32 (1908: June 5)
  - Item 33: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.33 (1908: June 12)
  - Item 34: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.34 (1908: June 19)
  - Item 35: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.35 (1908: June 26)
  - Item 36: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.36 (1908: July 3)
  - Item 37: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.37 (1908: July 10)
  - Item 38: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.38 (1908: July 17)
  - Item 39: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.39 (1908: July 24)
  - Item 40: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.40 (1908: July 31)
  - Item 41: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.41 (1908: Aug. 7)
  - Item 42: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.42 (1908: Aug. 14)
  - Item 43: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.43 (1908: Aug. 21)
  - Item 44: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.44 (1908: Aug. 28)
  - Item 45: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.45 (1908: Sept. 4)
  - Item 46: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.46 (1908: Sept. 11)
  - Item 47: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.47 (1908: Sept. 18)
  - Item 48: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.48 (1908: Sept. 25)
  - Item 49: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.49 (1908: Oct. 2)
  - Item 50: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.50 (1908: Oct. 9)
  - Item 51: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.51 (1908: Oct. 16)
  - Item 52: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.52 (1908: Oct. 23)
- Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908-1909 (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.1 (1908: Oct. 30)
  - Item 2: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.2 (1908: Nov. 6)
  - Item 3: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.3 (1908: Nov. 13)
  - Item 4: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.4 (1908: Nov. 20)
  - Item 5: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.5 (1908: Nov. 27)
  - Item 6: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.6 (1908: Dec. 4)
  - Item 7: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.7 (1908: Dec. 11)
  - Item 8: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.8 (1908: Dec. 18)
  - Item 9: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1908; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.9 (1908: Dec. 25)
  - Item 10: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.10 (1909: Jan. 1)
  - Item 11: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.11 (1909: Jan. 8)
  - Item 12: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.13 (1909: Jan. 22)
  - Item 13: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.14 (1909: Jan. 29)
  - Item 14: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.15 (1909: Feb. 5)
  - Item 15: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.16 (1909: Feb. 12)
  - Item 16: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.17 (1909: Feb. 19)
  - Item 17: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.18 (1909: Feb. 26)
  - Item 18: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.19 (1909: Mar. 5)
  - Item 19: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.20 (1909: Mar. 12)
  - Item 20: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.21 (1909: Mar. 19)
  - Item 21: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.22 (1909: Mar. 26)
  - Item 22: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.23 (1909: Apr. 2)
  - Item 23: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.24 (1909: Apr. 9)
  - Item 24: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.25 (1909: Apr. 16)
  - Item 25: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.26 (1909: Apr. 23)
  - Item 26: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.27 (1909: Apr. 30)
  - Item 27: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.28 (1909: May 7)
  - Item 28: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.29 (1909: May 14)
  - Item 29: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.30 (1909: May 21)
  - Item 30: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.31 (1909: May 28)
  - Item 31: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.32 (1909: June 4)
  - Item 32: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.33 (1909: June 11)
  - Item 33: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.35 (1909: June 25)
  - Item 34: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.36 (1909: July 2)
  - Item 35: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.37 (1909: July 9)
  - Item 36: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.38 (1909: July 16)
  - Item 37: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.39 (1909: July 23)
  - Item 38: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.40 (1909: July 30)
  - Item 39: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.41 (1909: Aug. 6)
  - Item 40: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.42 (1909: Aug. 13)
  - Item 41: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.43 (1909: Aug. 20)
  - Item 42: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.44 (1909: Aug. 27)
  - Item 43: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.45 (1909: Sept. 3)
  - Item 44: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.46 (1909: Sept. 10)
  - Item 45: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.47 (1909: Sept. 17)
  - Item 46: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.48 (1909: Sept. 24)
  - Item 47: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.49 (1909: Oct. 1)
  - Item 48: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.50 (1909: Oct. 8)
  - Item 49: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.51 (1909: Oct. 15)
  - Item 50: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.52 (1909: Oct. 22)
- Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909-1910 (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.1 (1909: Oct. 29)
  - Item 2: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.2 (1909: Nov. 5)
  - Item 3: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.3 (1909: Nov. 12)
  - Item 4: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.4 (1909: Nov. 19)
  - Item 5: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.5 (1909: Nov. 26)
  - Item 6: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.6 (1909: Dec. 3)
  - Item 7: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.7 (1909: Dec. 10)
  - Item 8: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.8 (1909: Dec. 17)
  - Item 9: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1909; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.9 (1909: Dec. 24)
  - Item 10: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.10 (1909: Dec. 31)
  - Item 11: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.12 (1910: Jan. 14)
  - Item 12: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.13 (1910: Jan. 21)
  - Item 13: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.14 (1910: Jan. 28)
  - Item 14: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.15 (1910: Feb. 4)
  - Item 15: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.16 (1910: Feb. 11)
  - Item 16: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.17 (1910: Feb. 18)
  - Item 17: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.18 (1910: Feb. 25)
  - Item 18: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.19 (1910: Mar. 4)
  - Item 19: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.20 (1910: Mar. 11)
  - Item 20: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.21 (1910: Mar. 18)
  - Item 21: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.22 (1910: Mar. 25)
  - Item 22: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.23 (1910: Apr. 1)
  - Item 23: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.24 (1910: Apr. 8)
  - Item 24: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.25 (1910: Apr. 15)
  - Item 25: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.26 (1910: Apr. 22)
  - Item 26: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.27 (1910: Apr. 29)
  - Item 27: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.28 (1910: May 6)
  - Item 28: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.29 (1910: May 13)
  - Item 29: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.30 (1910: May 20)
  - Item 30: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.31 (1910: May 27)
  - Item 31: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.32 (1910: June 3)
  - Item 32: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.33 (1910: June 10)
  - Item 33: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.34 (1910: June 17)
  - Item 34: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.35 (1910: June 24)
  - Item 35: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.36 (1910: July 1)
  - Item 36: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.37 (1910: July 8)
  - Item 37: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.38 (1910: July 15)
  - Item 38: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.10:no.40 (1911: July 28)
  - Item 39: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.10:no.41 (1911: Aug. 4)
  - Item 40: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.10:no.42 (1911: Aug. 11)
  - Item 41: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.10:no.43 (1911: Aug. 18)
  - Item 42: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.10:no.44 (1911: Aug. 25)
  - Item 43: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.10:no.50 (1911: Oct. 6)
  - Item 44: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.10:no.51 (1911: Oct. 13)
  - Item 45: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1910; Publication (Box 140, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.10:no.52 (1911: Oct. 20)
- West Coast Sailors, 1951; Publication (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: West Coast Sailors, 1951; Publication (Box 141, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.13:no.1 (1951: Jan. 19)
  - Item 2: West Coast Sailors, 1951; Publication (Box 141, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.13:no.2 (1951: Feb. 2)
  - Item 3: West Coast Sailors, 1951; Publication (Box 141, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.13:no.3 (1951: Feb. 16)
  - Item 4: West Coast Sailors, 1951; Publication (Box 141, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.13:no.4 (1951: Mar. 2)
  - Item 5: West Coast Sailors, 1951; Publication (Box 141, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.13:no.5 (1951: Mar. 16)
  - Item 6: West Coast Sailors, 1951; Publication (Box 141, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.13:no.6 (1951: Apr. 6)
  - Item 7: West Coast Sailors, 1951; Publication (Box 141, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.13:no.7 (1951: Apr. 20)
  - Item 8: West Coast Sailors, 1951; Publication (Box 141, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.13:no.8 (1951: May 4)
  - Item 9: West Coast Sailors, 1951; Publication (Box 141, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.13:no.9 (1951: May 18)
  - Item 10: West Coast Sailors, 1951; Publication (Box 141, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.13:no.10 (1951: June 1)
  - Item 11: West Coast Sailors, 1951; Publication (Box 141, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.13:no.11 (1951: June 15)
  - Item 12: West Coast Sailors, 1951; Publication (Box 141, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.13:no.12 (1951: June 29)
  - Item 13: West Coast Sailors, 1951; Publication (Box 141, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.13:no.13 (1951: July 13)
  - Item 14: West Coast Sailors, 1951; Publication (Box 141, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.13:no.14 (1951: July 27)
  - Item 15: West Coast Sailors, 1951; Publication (Box 141, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.13:no.15 (1951: Aug. 10)
  - Item 16: West Coast Sailors, 1951; Publication (Box 141, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.13:no.16 (1951: Aug. 24)
  - Item 17: West Coast Sailors, 1951; Publication (Box 141, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.13:no.17 (1951: Sept. 7)
  - Item 18: West Coast Sailors, 1951; Publication (Box 141, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.13:no.18 (1951: Sept. 21)
  - Item 19: West Coast Sailors, 1951; Publication (Box 141, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.13:no.19 (1951: Oct. 5)
  - Item 20: West Coast Sailors, 1951; Publication (Box 141, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.13:no.20 (1951: Oct. 19)
  - Item 21: West Coast Sailors, 1951; Publication (Box 141, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.13:no.21 (1951: Nov. 16)
  - Item 22: West Coast Sailors, 1951; Publication (Box 141, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.13:no.22 (1951: Nov. 30)
  - Item 23: West Coast Sailors, 1951; Publication (Box 141, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.13:no.23 (1951: Dec. 14)
  - Item 24: West Coast Sailors, 1951; Publication (Box 141, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.13:no.24 (1951: Dec. 28)
  - Item 25: West Coast Sailors, 1951; Publication (Box 141, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.13:no.25 (1951: Dec. 28)
- West Coast Sailors, 1952; Publication (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: West Coast Sailors, 1952; Publication (Box 141, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.14:no.1 (1952: Jan. 11)
  - Item 2: West Coast Sailors, 1952; Publication (Box 141, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.14:no.2 (1952: Jan. 25)
  - Item 3: West Coast Sailors, 1952; Publication (Box 141, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.14:no.3 (1952: Feb. 8)
  - Item 4: West Coast Sailors, 1952; Publication (Box 141, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.14:no.4 (1952: Feb. 14)
  - Item 5: West Coast Sailors, 1952; Publication (Box 141, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.14:no.5 (1952: Mar. 7)
  - Item 6: West Coast Sailors, 1952; Publication (Box 141, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.14:no.6 (1952: Mar. 21)
  - Item 7: West Coast Sailors, 1952; Publication (Box 141, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.14:no.7 (1952: Apr. 4)
  - Item 8: West Coast Sailors, 1952; Publication (Box 141, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.14:no.8 (1952: Apr. 18)
  - Item 9: West Coast Sailors, 1952; Publication (Box 141, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.14:no.9 (1952: May 2)
  - Item 10: West Coast Sailors, 1952; Publication (Box 141, Folder 2)